const superData = [{
  "id": 1,
  "question": "What planet does Superman come from?",
  "answers": ["Krypton", "Rann", "Thanagar"],
  "correctAnswer": "Krypton"
}, {
  "id": 2,
  "question": "Who shot Batman's parents?",
  "answers": ["Joe Chill", "Matches Malone", "The Joker"],
  "correctAnswer": "Joe Chill"
}, {
  "id": 3,
  "question": "What turned Bruce Banner into the Hulk",
  "answers": ["cosmic radiation", "gamma rays", "unstable molecules"],
  "correctAnswer": "gamma rays"
}, {
  "id": 4,
  "question": "What is color is Wonder Woman's airplane?",
  "answers": ["gold", "red", "invisible"],
  "correctAnswer": "invisible"
}, {
  "id": 5,
  "question": "What burrough is Spiderman from?",
  "answers": ["Queens", "Harlem", "Brooklyn"],
  "correctAnswer": "Queens"
}, {
  "id": 6,
  "question": "What is the headquarters of the Green Lantern Corp. called?",
  "answers": ["EGO", "OA", "MOGO"],
  "correctAnswer": "OA"
}, {
  "id": 7,
  "question": "Where does Doctor Doom live?",
  "answers": ["Latveria", "Wakanda", "Markovia"],
  "correctAnswer": "Latveria"
}, {
  "id": 8,
  "question": "What gives The Flash his speed?",
  "answers": ["diet/exercise", "speed serum", "the speed force"],
  "correctAnswer": "the speed force"
}, {
  "id": 9,
  "question": "Who was Captain America's partner in WWII?",
  "answers": ["Snapper Carr", "Bucky Barnes", "Rick Jones"],
  "correctAnswer": "Bucky Barnes"
}, {
  "id": 10,
  "question": "What was The Wasp's other career?",
  "answers": ["spy", "fashion designer", "doctor"],
  "correctAnswer": "fashion designer"
}, {
  "id": 11,
  "question": "In what building do the Fantastic Four live?",
  "answers": ["The Fortress of Solitude", "The Helicarrier", "The Baxter Building"],
  "correctAnswer": "The Baxter Building"
}, {
  "id": 12,
  "question": "Who was the first Robin?",
  "answers": ["Dick Grayson", "Tim Drake", "Jason Todd"],
  "correctAnswer": "Dick Grayson"
}, {
  "id": 13,
  "question": "Aquaman can talk to fish.",
  "answers": ["true", "false"],
  "correctAnswer": "true"
}, {
  "id": 14,
  "question": "The X-Men are all mutants, otherwise known as:",
  "answers": ["inhumans", "homo-superior", "homo-mutanimal"],
  "correctAnswer": "homo-superior"
}, {
  "id": 15,
  "question": "Where did Tony Stark become Iron Man?",
  "answers": ["Malibu", "Vietnam", "Outer Space"],
  "correctAnswer": "Vietnam"
}, {
  "id": 16,
  "question": "Who was the Herald of Galactus?",
  "answers": ["The Spectre", "The Living Tribunal", "The Silver Surfer"],
  "correctAnswer": "The Silver Surfer"
}, {
  "id": 17,
  "question": "Which dog can teleport?",
  "answers": ["Lockjaw", "Krypto", "Ace the Bat-Hound"],
  "correctAnswer": "Lockjaw"
}, {
  "id": 18,
  "question": "What are Wolverine's bones covered in?",
  "answers": ["vibranium", "nth metal", "adamantium"],
  "correctAnswer": "adamantium"
}, {
  "id": 19,
  "question": "What kind of animal was the Justice Leagues first villain?",
  "answers": ["gorilla", "starfish", "t-rex"],
  "correctAnswer": "starfish"
}, {
  "id": 20,
  "question": "Professor X can read minds",
  "answers": ["true", "false"],
  "correctAnswer": "true"
}, {
  "id": 21,
  "question": "What group did Nick Fury lead in WWII?",
  "answers": ["The Howling Commandos", "The Freedom Fighters", "The Invaders"],
  "correctAnswer": "The Howling Commandos"
}, {
  "id": 22,
  "question": "What is Batgirl's secret identity?",
  "answers": ["Jessica Jones", "Barbara Gordon", "Susan Storm"],
  "correctAnswer": "Barbara Gordon"
}, {
  "id": 23,
  "question": "What sense is Daredevil lacking?",
  "answers": ["hearing", "smell", "sight"],
  "correctAnswer": "sight"
}, {
  "id": 24,
  "question": "The Thing can turn back into a normal person",
  "answers": ["true", "false"],
  "correctAnswer": "false"
}, {
  "id": 25,
  "question": "Batman has a butler named Jarvis.",
  "answers": ["true", "false"],
  "correctAnswer": "false"
}, {
  "id": 26,
  "question": "Who was the first superhero team?",
  "answers": ["The Fantastic Four", "The Crimebusters", "The Justice Society"],
  "correctAnswer": "The Justice Society"
}, {
  "id": 27,
  "question": "Doctor Strange is a real doctor.",
  "answers": ["true", "false"],
  "correctAnswer": "true"
}, {
  "id": 28,
  "question": "Where is J'onn J'onzz from?",
  "answers": ["Mars", "Counter Earth", "Niburu"],
  "correctAnswer": "Mars"
}, {
  "id": 29,
  "question": "This X-man was the first to become an Avenger.",
  "answers": ["Storm", "Wolverine", "Beast"],
  "correctAnswer": "Beast"
}, {
  "id": 30,
  "question": "Who was the first Captain Marvel?",
  "answers": ["Mar Vell", "Carol Danvers", "Billy Batson"],
  "correctAnswer": "Billy Batson"
}]

module.exports = {
  superData 
}